Matt Haney

Honest, Hardworking, Principaled employee.

Asheville, NC mthaney4@gmail.com +1(828) 4903406

I am an avid learner. I love anything related to technology. I have interest in web development, robotics, design, coding, 3d animation, Linux, and all things related to computers or tech.

I am experienced in marketing (in both for-profit and non-profit sectors), web-development, graphic design, and SEO. I have Google certification in marketing / advertising, and Google Cloud. I am a die hard Linux enthusiast! If it powers on, I can master it.

- Digital Marketing Specialist
- · Google Cloud Digital Leader
- Google Cloud Security and Operations
- Infrastructure and Application Modernization with Google Cloud
- Innovating with Data and Google Cloud
- Digital Transformation with Google Cloud
- Generative AI
- Encoder-Decoder Architecture
- · Attention Mechanism
- · Al Media Generation

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Certified Google Cloud Digital Leader

Google-Leesburg, FL January 2023 to Present

- Digital transformation with Google Cloud
- Innovating with data and Google Cloud
- Infrastructure and application modernization
- · Google Cloud security and operations

CNC Machinist/Programmer

INC-Leesburg, FL January 2018 to Present

3D Design, 3D Carving, CNC Operator, Sign Designer & Creator, CNC Routing, Computer Repair, Programming

Marketing Director / Web Developer

Math technology-Leesburg, FL January 2006 to Present

WordPress development

Web design

Google marketing
Social media marketing
3d design
Motion graphics
Graphic design
Video editing
Linux contribution
Open source software

Director of Communications / Teacher

The Genesis Center-Leesburg, FL January 2013 to January 2021

Managed All Digital and Print Communications Marketing (digital & physical)

Web Development
Audio Visual
Technology Repair & Upkeep
3D Design
Graphic Design
Animation

3D Design build designer & Technology Manager

PSL CONSTRUCTION-Wildwood, FL January 2012 to January 2018

Drafted Blueprints, developed website, fixed computers, graphic design, marketing, advertising, built custom lumber cost comparison software saving company 6 million, and phone app.

Student - Various

Liberty University January 2006 to January 2012

College & law school

Maintenance Supervisor

Avante Nursing Home-Leesburg, FL January 2004 to January 2006

Repair and facility upkeep

Painter/Crew Leader

Lawyer paint-Leicester, NC January 1998 to January 2004

Interior and exterior painter. Supervisor role after 3 years.

Google Certified Advertising Specialist

self-employed-Leesburg, FL January 2020

I have Google digital marketing and advertising certification.

Education

2nd year law in Property Law

Liberty University School of Law 2010 to 2012

B.S. in Consumer Psychology

Liberty University 2006 to 2009

Skills

- Computer Programming
- Architectural Design
- General Contractor
- Elementary Education
- All things Computer Matt Haney -
- WordPress
- CAD
- HTML5
- Robotics
- Computer Skills
- Computer Literacy
- Computer Graphics
- Computer Repair
- Application Development
- IT Experience
- IT Support
- Graphic Design
- Linux
- Web Design
- Web Development
- SEO
- Marketing
- · Digital Marketing
- · Robot Programming
- Teaching Experience
- 3D Applications
- Audio Editing
- Mechanical Knowledge
- · Machine Operator

- Data Analysis Skills
- Report Preparation
- Software Development
- Database Development
- Git
- APIs
- Video Editing
- JavaScript
- User Interface (UI)
- · Google Ads
- Google Marketing Platform
- Google Ad Manager
- Bing Ads
- Facebook Advertising
- Google Analytics
- PPC Campaign Management
- Email Marketing
- Analytics
- MySQL
- 3D Animation
- Google AdWords
- Windows
- Gnu
- Google Cloud Digital Leader (5 years)
- Google Cloud Platform (5 years)
- · Graphic design
- Video editing
- Web design
- WordPress
- Social media management
- Motion graphics
- SEO
- HTML5
- Marketing
- · Digital marketing
- Facebook Advertising
- Google Analytics
- Web development
- Google Ads
- 3D animation

- Bing Ads
- JavaScript
- Application development
- Sketchup
- Computer graphics
- Git
- Project management
- Linux
- CAD
- Drafting
- · Customer service
- AutoCAD
- Construction
- Al
- IT
- Software development
- · Robot programming
- E-commerce
- Data analysis skills
- A/B testing
- Email marketing
- CSS
- Keyword research
- Analysis skills
- Marketing automation
- Analytics
- Responsive web design
- Content marketing
- · Google AdWords
- · Content creation
- Content management systems
- Microsoft Office
- Kitchen experience
- Copywriting
- Communication skills
- Writing skills
- Word processing
- Microsoft Powerpoint
- Adobe InDesign
- Computer skills

- · Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Website management
- Market research
- Front-end development
- Computer operation
- Schematics
- Metal building erection
- CNC
- Manufacturing
- CNC laser cutting
- Mechanical knowledge
- Hand tools
- Supervising experience
- Mentoring
- Human resources
- Training & development
- Technical support
- Project management software
- Photography
- Renovation
- · Residential construction
- Lead generation
- PPC Campaign Management
- SEO tools
- Media buying
- SEM
- Google Suite
- PHP
- Math
- Tutoring
- Education administration
- Research
- · Proofreading
- Leadership
- React
- Windows
- Node.js

https://giphy.com/channel/mthprblm

https://www.cloudskillsboost.google/public_profiles/683742c6-80d0-4bc8-ae91-c2944e81cc8d

Certifications and Licenses

Google Digital Marketing Specialist

January 2020 to Present

Google Cloud Digital Leader

January 2023 to Present

- Digital transformation with Google Cloud
- · Innovating with data and Google Cloud
- Infrastructure and application modernization
- Google Cloud security and operations

Driver's License

Assessments

Legal skills — Proficient

October 2022

Supporting legal procedures, preparing documents, doing research, and collecting client information in a legal setting

Full results: Proficient

Construction safety — Proficient

September 2022

Using safe practices while on a construction site

Full results: Proficient

Outside sales — Proficient

October 2022

Understanding and responding appropriately in sales scenarios, and performing common sales calculations

Full results: Proficient

Case management & social work — Proficient

September 2022

Determining client needs, providing support resources, and collaborating with clients and multidisciplinary teams

Full results: Proficient

Sales skills — Proficient

December 2022

Influencing and negotiating with customers

Full results: Proficient

Working with MS Word documents — Proficient

September 2022

Knowledge of various Microsoft Word features, functions, and techniques

Full results: Proficient

Workplace safety — Proficient

September 2022

Using safe practices at work

Full results: Proficient

Attention to detail — Proficient

December 2022

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting

information

Full results: Proficient

Data entry: Attention to detail — Proficient

November 2023

Maintaining data integrity by detecting errors

Full results: Proficient

Typing — Proficient

September 2022
Transcribing text
Full results: Proficient

Supervisory skills: Motivating & assessing employees — Proficient

September 2022

Motivating others to achieve objectives and identifying improvements or corrective actions

Full results: Proficient

Software developer fit — Proficient

September 2022

Measures the traits that are important for successful software developers

Full results: Proficient

Retail customer service — Proficient

September 2022

Responding to customer situations in a retail setting

Full results: Proficient

Technical support — Proficient

September 2022

Performing software, hardware, and network operations

Full results: Proficient

Analyzing data — **Proficient**

September 2022

Interpreting and producing graphs, identifying trends, and drawing justifiable conclusions from data

Full results: Proficient

Marketing — **Proficient**

March 2023

Understanding a target audience and how to best communicate with them

Full results: Proficient

Proofreading — **Proficient**

September 2022

Finding and correcting errors in written texts

Full results: Proficient

Basic maintenance and repair — Proficient

September 2022

Performing basic repairs and maintenance for apartment complexes, office buildings, and other

facilities

Full results: Proficient

Marketing — Proficient

August 2022

Understanding a target audience and how to best communicate with them

Full results: Proficient

Learning agility — Proficient

September 2022

Learning and applying new information

Full results: Proficient

Graphic design — Proficient

October 2023

Using graphic design techniques and producing visual media to communicate concepts

Full results: Proficient

Project timeline management — Proficient

September 2022

Prioritizing and allocating time to effectively achieve project deliverables

Full results: Proficient

Social media — Proficient

August 2022

Knowledge of social media techniques and analytics interpretation

Full results: Proficient

Basic computer skills — Proficient

September 2022

Performing basic computer operations and troubleshooting common problems

Full results: Proficient

Mechanical knowledge — Proficient

May 2022

Understanding and applying mechanical concepts and processes

Full results: Proficient

Manufacturing skills — Proficient

March 2024

Monitoring systems, reading schematics, and using tools that are commonly found in a manufacturing setting

Full results: Proficient

Work style: Reliability - Proficient

September 2022

Tendency to be reliable, dependable, and act with integrity at work

Full results: Proficient

Attention to detail — Proficient

October 2023

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting

information

Full results: Proficient

Management & leadership skills: Impact & influence — Proficient

September 2022

Choosing the most effective strategy to inspire and influence others to meet business objectives

Full results: Proficient

Work style: Reliability — Proficient

September 2023

Tendency to be reliable, dependable, and act with integrity at work

Full results: Proficient

Forklift safety — Proficient

September 2022

Best practices and safety hazards in forklift operation

Full results: Proficient

Written communication — Proficient

September 2022

Best practices for writing, including grammar, style, clarity, and brevity

Full results: Proficient

Social media — Proficient

October 2023

Knowledge of social media techniques and analytics interpretation

Full results: Proficient

Management & leadership skills: Planning & execution — Proficient

September 2022

Planning and managing resources to accomplish organizational goals

Full results: Proficient

Manufacturing fit — Proficient

March 2023

Measures the traits that are important for success in manufacturing roles

Full results: Proficient

Customer focus & orientation — Proficient

September 2022

Responding to customer situations with sensitivity

Full results: Proficient

Automotive maintenance — Proficient

September 2022

Knowledge of vehicles, vehicle maintenance, and repairs

Full results: Proficient

HR: Compensation & benefits — Proficient

September 2022

Knowledge of compensation and benefits programs

Full results: Proficient

Basic maintenance and repair — Proficient

March 2023

Performing basic repairs and maintenance for apartment complexes, office buildings, and other

facilities

Full results: Proficient

Warehouse shift leader — Proficient

September 2022

Supervising warehouse staff and maintaining safety and security standards

Full results: Proficient

Technical support: Customer situations — Proficient

September 2022

Responding to technical support situations with sensitivity

Full results: Proficient

Office manager — Proficient

October 2022

Scheduling and budgeting Full results: Proficient

Teamwork: Interpersonal skills — Proficient

September 2022

Responding to challenging team situations at work

Full results: Proficient

Sales skills — Proficient

May 2022

Influencing and negotiating with customers

Full results: Proficient

Work style: Professionalism — Proficient

October 2022

Tendency to be accountable, professional, open to feedback, and act with integrity at work

Full results: Proficient

Filing & organization — Proficient

September 2022

Arranging and managing information or materials using a set of rules

Full results: Proficient

Spreadsheets with Microsoft Excel — Proficient

September 2022

Knowledge of various Microsoft Excel features, functions, and formulas

Full results: Proficient

Bookkeeping — Proficient

October 2022

Calculating and determining the accuracy of financial data

Full results: Proficient

Warehouse safety — Proficient

September 2022

Using safe practices in a warehouse setting

Full results: Proficient

Business math — Proficient

September 2022

Using basic math to solve problems in a business context

Full results: Proficient

Attention to detail — Proficient

May 2022

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting

information

Full results: Proficient

Customer service — Proficient

October 2022

Identifying and resolving common customer issues

Full results: Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.